<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Amirul Abdul Aziz</title>
    <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Amirul Abdul Aziz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification using CNN</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-3/</guid>
      <description>This project is my final project submission on Lintasarta DigiSchool 2021 machine learning developer scholarship program. This project is about image classification using a dataset that contains various hands from different races, ages, and genders, posed into rock/paper/scissors and labeled. The Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) model was utilized for classifying the image data into the correct class of target data. The data was provided by dicoding.com and then will be extracted and split into two folders, train and val, with a ratio of 60:40.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Personal Loan Modelling</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-2/</guid>
      <description>This project is about a bank which has a growing customer base where the majority of customers are depositors with varying size of deposits. Apart from the majority of customers that are depositors, several customers are also borrowers (asset customers). The bank planned to expand the asset customers to earn more through the interest on personal loans by converting the depositors (potential customers) to personal loan customers while retaining them as depositors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Learning Implementation for Electrofacies, Lithofacies, and Depositional Environment Prediction using K-Nearest Neighbors Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-1/</guid>
      <description>In this recent years, digitalization and automation have been massively transforming and leads global industries to a new era of technology. In line with the technology improvement, there is a high growth of interest in utilizing data to extract an insight that hopes will be an advantage for the industries to reach their objectives. This positive phenomenon also applies in the petroleum industry by utilizing machine learning to aid exploration activities, commercial decision making, and analyze past data to extract unseen data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nickel Laterite Exploration and Exploitation as Metals Resources Optimization and Indonesian Industry Support</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>The Indonesian region, which developed from an active and complex tectonic mechanism, has indirectly positive and negative impacts on this country. The negative impact experienced by the country is felt when plate movements occur in Indonesian territory, causing earthquakes and other geological disasters. However, the positive impact is that Indonesia gets long-term benefits that can be considered as a country natural asset, thanks to its tectonic and topographical patterns, namely the existence of mineralization pathways that cause abundant nickel laterite resources which are scattered in several regions of Indonesia, especially on the island of Sulawesi where if these natural resources are properly managed they can meet the needs of the community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
