<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aziz&#39;s Portfolio on Amirul Abdul Aziz</title>
    <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aziz&#39;s Portfolio on Amirul Abdul Aziz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nickel Laterite Exploration and Exploitation as Metals Resources Optimization and Indonesian Industry Support</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>The Indonesian region, which developed from an active and complex tectonic mechanism, has indirectly positive and negative impacts on this country. The negative impact experienced by the country is felt when plate movements occur in Indonesian territory, causing earthquakes and other geological disasters. However, the positive impact is that Indonesia gets long-term benefits that can be considered as a country natural asset, thanks to its tectonic and topographical patterns, namely the existence of mineralization pathways that cause abundant nickel laterite resources which are scattered in several regions of Indonesia, especially on the island of Sulawesi where if these natural resources are properly managed they can meet the needs of the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Latest Earthquake Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/projects/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Tools: Python, Numpy, Plotly, Matplotlib, pandas, seaborn
Earthquake data might be one of the most important data that ever recorded by humans. Proper utilization of earthquake data could significantly save a million lives and reduce earthquake damage. Apart from natural events, earthquakes also can be induced by human activities in form of fluids injection on oil and gas wells, surface and underground mining activities, or explosions.
Using the past 30 days, from December 26, 2020, to January 25, 2021, earthquake events data around the world that I’ve got from the USGS website, I tried to analyze and visualize the dataset to determined several objectives such as, identify the most dominant earthquake magnitude values that have occurred for the past 30 days, analyze the dominant depth where the earthquake has occurred and it’s relation to data reliability, and visualize the earthquake data on the world map to identify the region where the earthquake has occurred for the past 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azizamir.github.io/portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to discuss more on my project or interested in working together, please fill out the form below. I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
